Thank you. Thank you. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. The first time we met, we were playing a game called the The first time we met, we were playing a game called the The first time we met, we were playing a game called the The first time we met, we were playing a game called the The first time we met, we were playing a game called the
The first time we met, we were playing a game called the
The first time we met, we were playing a game called the The first time we met, we were playing a game called the The first time we met, we were playing a game called the The first time we met, we were playing a game called the The first time we met, we are playing Suikamani!
We've been around 10 times!
Why are you so rude? Let's play rock-paper-scissors!
But we can't break it in one try.
Okay, then.
Can you show us a little more?
Left, left.
How do you do it?
Everyone, uh, what?
Friends? Don't come here. We are going to turn right and left. Left, left, left. Are you guys friends?
Don't come here.
Turn the clock.
Here?
Not here.
Go, go, go.
Turn right.
Turn the clock.
I know the clock.
Go, go! Here?
The front!
A little more clock!
Here?
You can't change your place!
Right?
I'm good now!
Really?
Nobody's here, right. There's no one here.
There's a watermelon.
Turn right.
Here?
Ready?
It's hard.
It's hard to get a watermelon.
Was it bad?
Try it.
I'm scared.
It's hard!
As far as I remember...
I don't remember when I did it last.
So...
Should we go to the starting position?
Sure.
It's getting cooler.
You didn't go that far.
No way.
That's it.
Around here.
Good evening.
Turn around 10 times.
Hello. Can you count? Good evening. Turn around 10 times. Say hello.
Hello.
The wind is strong.
Wait, Shiorin.
Shiorin is late.
I'm late.
Shiorin is black.
I'm so scared it. I understand.
I'm completely white.
Look at me.
Ren-chan.
Chie-chan.
Look at me.
I can't do it.
I can't help it.
You can do it.
I can't do it.
Yes.
OK.
I'm sorry.
OK. I'll I'm scared!
OK, you can go.
Go forward.
Turn the clock.
90 degrees.
OK.
Wait.
Your eyes are too big.
Grandma!
I can't do it.
My eyes are spinning.
You were so excited.
Grandma. I can't do it. My eyes so excited! I can't do it!
My eyes are spinning!
Your eyes are spinning! Are you okay?
Okay, okay!
Go straight like this.
You're losing to the wind.
Turn left a little bit.
That's good.
Should I go one more step?
Here it comes.
Around the clock.
Good.
A little more to the right.
I'll split it.
Ready, go.
It's difficult.
Will it shake?
It didn't hit.
It's going to hit.
It's a little... It's difficult. I didn't hit it. I think I hit it. I think I hit it. But... But...
I got a little dented.
It's difficult.
Do it.
I want to do it.
Let's do it at the end.
Do it with your strength.
Do it at the end.
I can't see.
You did it last year.
I did it at the end.
You did it.
Really?
You did it last year.
I'll do it.
Look at me.
It's really difficult.
What?
I'm begging you, Kanako.
Wait a minute. Turn around 10 times.
It's like a magician.
A magician.
One more time.
4, 5,
Hey, Mom! It's 7, 8, 9, 10 10 10? Start! Wait a second
Ma-chan, Ma-chan
Ma-chan!
I can't do it
You're going to fall
I didn't tell you to do it
I didn't tell you
I didn't say anything
Don't bite me Don't bite me I'm not a I'm not a I'm not a I'm not a I'm not a
I'm not a
I'm not a I'm not a I'm not a I little more. I'm too strong. That's right.
You can put your leg forward.
That's good.
That's great.
Do it with all your strength.
Ready, go!
Ah!
It's a little bit off.
It's difficult.
It's a little bit off. It's a little dangerous. I'm a little scared.
I'm a little scared.
Let's do it at the end.
There are quite a few eyes.
If you have a blind spot.
Wait a minute.
It's hard.
It's dangerous.
Wait a minute.
Thank you.
This way. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 52, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 53, 5 6 It's raining! 7
The wind is strong.
Start!
Go for it! Go for it! Straight, straight!
Good!
Scary!
I'm going too!
Right, right!
Straight, straight!
A little more!
Right, right!
It's close.
Right, right, right.
Right turn.
Good.
Do you want to go with that short?
A little bit more.
Right, right, right.
You should go like that.
It's okay. Right, right, right. You should go like that. It's okay.
Right, right.
Go!
Ready, go!
No!
Let's do it again.
Left, left.
Ready, go!
Where? Ready?
Ready?
Go!
Nice!
It's a pinnacle hit!
Amazing!
But it won't break.
It won't!
It's big!
It's a big watermelon!
We did it!
It's big!
Let's eat this watermelon. Let's eat it! We ate it! So, let's eat this watermelon!
Let's eat!
Eat it over there.
It's a big watermelon.
It's on the table.
Then, please take care of the watermelon.
Please.
We did it!
I don't know the rules of the game. I was surprised. Thank you. Thank you.
I'm glad.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking. It's so cute. It's a I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It was difficult.
Can I eat it?
It's okay.
I'll eat it. I'll eat it. It's good. It's good. You don't have any seeds? Let's eat.
Let's eat.
Did you eat the watermelon this year?
Yes, I did.
You ate a lot.
I ate a lot.
Let's eat.
It's sweet.
It's delicious.
Arin is big.
You're the biggest one.
It's so good!
It's so sweet!
It's 0 calories for two.
It's not fair.
I'm the only one who can eat it. It's unfair.
I like this part without seeds.
I like the part without seeds.
It's too sweet.
Is there any other part you can eat?
No.
No?
I don't have any seeds.
I removed the seeds. You're so kind.
Everyone gives me seeds.
Yay.
Did you all eat the watermelon this summer?
Summer is over.
It's the end of August.
It's getting cooler at night.
Last time, we had a hot-air balloon...
Oh, sorry.
What?
Hot-air balloon.
No, no, no. No, no, no. No, no, sorry. What? Fantasy.
If you remember it, do it properly.
I know.
Like this.
It's too long.
Yay.
Sorry.
That's all for today. Let will enjoy the end of summer.
We will enjoy the end of summer and deliver a lot.
It says that we go to BBQ wherever we go.
We will also do BBQ.
Delivery from a fashionable atmosphere.
It's getting cooler.
But it was hot in the afternoon.
It was hot.
I've been with RENI since noon today.
That's right.
RENI was sweating from the face for a moment after eating and getting on the car.
It was so hot.
It was really hot.
It's hot.
It's still summer, so it's going to be hot next month.
It's going to be hot.
The festival is still hot.
It's definitely hot in September.
It's pretty cool now.
It says it's only on YouTube, but is it only on YouTube?
Only on YouTube?
TikTok starts at 23.30.
Oh, it starts in the middle.
Sorry, I made a mistake.
I'm going home.
It's midnight.
I don't want to go home.
It's pretty late.
Sorry.
Did you get a toothache?
It's not a toothache.
What do you mean?
Hey.
What? What do you mean? Does it mean you have a tooth. What do you mean? I don't know.
Do you ever get a toothache?
It looks fun.
It looks fun to get a toothache.
No, it's not.
I think it's a tooth because it's on the person who gave it to me.
What was it?
It was this.
It's a Yaring. It's almost a tooth.
It's not a tooth.
It's white.
How was your summer?
Not much.
What did you do?
It's been a while since I met you.
Really?
I haven't seen you for about two weeks. I think so. Kanako. Really? Yes, I think so.
I think we haven't met for two weeks.
We met on the radio.
We met only once.
Twice.
Once?
You remember it well.
Kanako remembers it better than I do.
Twice.
You count it.
Did you do anything summery?
Something summery?
Yes.
I asked Neri-chan about my summer memories and she has a lot of them.
Neri-chan did BBQ, went to fireworks festival, went to zoo, went to dinosaur shop.
More than 4?
Amazing.
You went to the Univ.
I went to the Univ.
Amazing. It's summer.
I played a lot.
You played a lot. That's amazing. It's summer. We played a lot. You did.
That's good.
I didn't get to talk.
I ate a lot of watermelon.
You ate watermelon?
The watermelon I got was big.
It was really big.
Yes, yes.
The teacher at the school.
She's a high school teacher.
She sends a big watermelon to each member every year.
Thank you teacher.
I enjoyed it.
It's really big.
When I cut it, it broke in the middle.
I cut it.
I cut it too.
How big is this knife?
Everyone is eating.
Why?
It's not funny.
What are you doing?
Make-san and I are eating.
I'm surprised.
Is it delicious?
It's good.
Please look at me.
Is there something on your teeth? Make-san's nice. Wait a minute. That's nice. Look at me. Don't you have something on your teeth?
It's your job.
It looks like pizza.
It's fun.
It's nice.
Everyone is having fun.
Everyone has played golf.
Yes.
They ate melon.
Golf in summer is hot.
Have you played golf?
I have. But you haven't played in August. We went to the golf course. We did.
But we didn't go in August.
We did in July.
It was hot.
We tried to go in August, but we couldn't.
We told everyone to stop.
They said it's hot so we should stop.
This summer is especially hot.
We say that every year. Especially this summer. I'm told that every year.
There is a place with a cart with a cooler.
Isn't it cool?
I want to ride it.
Everyone said they went to the hot spring.
I went to the hot spring.
I have a Toy Story.
It's really good.
I went to the name.
Fantasy Spring.
I want to go to the fireworks festival in Kameoka.
We had a live show at the first festival of spring.
They used Momokuru's song at the fireworks festival.
They used fireworks and a girl who is a street girl.
Thank you. I heard you used fireworks and the girl from Kaito.
Thank you.
Chami-chan showed me the video.
Chami-chan is a volunteer at Kamioka.
She showed me a lot of videos.
I'm glad. I haven't been to a fireworks show.
I heard the sound and... The sound was from the I could see the fireworks and the fireworks.
I did it.
Let's show them the fireworks.
Can you show me the fireworks?
Wow, it's beautiful.
It's beautiful.
You can change seats.
The fireworks look better when they are a little far apart.
I wanted the sound. to hear the sound.
Then, do it.
Why?
Sound.
Here I go.
Your face.
I was looking that way.
You were looking this way. You're looking at me.
Did you enjoy the summer?
Yes, I did.
It was great.
I'm enjoying it now.
Right.
It's a crazy wind.
I like the night breeze at the end of the summer.
It's nice.
It's romantic.
The night is nice. It's a good night. It's a good night. It's a good night.
It's good.
I want you to cut it now.
Only that moment.
It was romantic.
And it was a little over here.
The elbow that was in here.
And it was windy.
It was good.
I'm embarrassed.
It was a drama. It was a drama.
You're prettier than me.
Everyone is saying that.
There is an announcement here.
It's a bit loose.
There is a serious announcement.
We want to deliver this to everyone. That's right. We have a serious announcement.
We want to deliver this to everyone.
That's right.
We are very excited.
First, please watch this VTR.
Please watch it.
The wind is strong.
Next Live is scheduled to be held.
Yay!
This was announced.
Yes. On December 21st, 22nd.
Saitama
Arena
Mokuri 2024
So...
It's not a fireworks now.
Oh, it's not a fireworks.
Parappara
Yes! So, once again. No, not Hanabi. Oh, it's ***. Parappara.
So, once again,
December 21st, Saturday and 22nd, Sunday,
Momoiro Christmas 2024 will be held.
The venue is Saitama Super Arena.
I'm happy.
Thank you for your hard work.
Christmas is a must.
It's a little early without this. Yes, that's right.
But I'm happy to spend Christmas with everyone again this year.
Yes, we have the details now.
Yes!
It's 11 o'clock on the 21st.
It's 16 o'clock on the 22nd.
There are three types of tickets at Showa Saitama Super Arena.
Yes! There are three types of tickets. The ticket is the first reception of the Angel Eyes members.
It's after 21 o'clock today.
It's about 1 hour and 45 minutes.
It will be from 21 o'clock to 9th, 1st, Sunday, and 20th, 30th, and 59th.
It's a little over a week.
Yes.
Everyone says that it was a
little over a week.
Yes.
It's a Christmas concert, so it's a different Christmas.
But the content is a new challenge.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think we can announce it in detail.
Please look forward to it.
Sometimes it's a little cut off.
Is that okay?
If you missed something, please check the official website
I think the red one will remain
If you don't say anything
The fireworks were banned
Why?
Let's say it again, Kana-chan. Yes, yes.
On December 21st, 2024,
Saturday and Sunday, 22nd,
at Saitama Super Arena,
we will be holding
Momoiro Christmas 2024.
Today,
before the live stream,
we have a meeting.
Yes, that's right.
It's like we're right. Let's start.
It's still hot.
I have to think about the free sauce.
It's really quick.
I thought there were only 4 months left this year.
Rei-chan.
If you don't say Shintonshan, the archive will be left.
I might say that again.
If I remember that.
It's no good. I can't.
I didn't leave it in the archive.
I didn't leave it.
I'm still getting goosebumps.
It's scary.
I'm scared.
I'll be careful.
Everyone is a chintonsha.
I want to enjoy the summer.
Then, is it okay to eat?
What?
I don't know.
Maybe you have eyes on something else.
I know.
Look.
It smells good.
RUMI is the closest.
Yes, she is the I'm hungry. There's a lot of meat there.
It's your birthday.
21st or 22nd is your birthday, right?
Congratulations.
I'm so hungry.
TikTok live is starting.
It's already 21.30.
We'll start TikTok live.
I'm glad we didn't announce it on TikTok live.
I'm glad we didn to announce it on TikTok live
Oh, it's written
Thank you
Let's do it again, Jessie
Yes
A-chan is
Everyone is filming on TikTok live
A-chan, come here
A-chan
Yes
Yes, yes
Is it starting?
It hasn't started yet.
Sorry, it's a rumor.
Sorry.
It's not a rumor, sorry.
It's like a rumor.
It's a new generation.
Everyone is a new generation, right?
Yes.
Wow, there are a lot of people. Yes, we are. We are the members of the Mikitoku Live. Wow, there are so many of you!
Good evening! Are you watching?
Today, we are streaming live on Momokuro's official YouTube channel.
Shall we announce it?
We just announced it on YouTube.
Our Christmas Live.
We will hold the Momoiro Christmas 2024 for two days on December 21st and Saturday, 22nd, 2024.
The venue is Saitama Super Arena.
It's SSA! We are SSA! So, we are going to do a live performance of Momocro.
This year, we didn't have a summer performance.
So, we are going to do a live performance of four members.
We are not sure if we can do it.
No, no.
A little more.
Close your eyes.
OK.
How to clap is also an aunt
One by one
After this, the fan club pre-order will be received from 9 o'clock
Please check it out
Please
The wind is strong, so we're going to eat inside.
Let's move.
Let's go.
We'll eat this later.
It's a barbecue.
I can't stand it.
It's hot. Let's eat.
Let's eat.
Is this okay?
Thank you.
See you later.
We will eat together.
Let's eat together.
Let's eat together. Let's eat together. Do you want to come with us? Yes, I want to come with you. If you leave it here...
I want to eat it.
I have something to eat.
It looks delicious.
It's hot.
It's here.
You're eating normally.
It's a meal.
Wait, what's that? It's a meal. It's a war. Wait, what's that?
Salmon!
It looks so good.
It's hot.
I'm happy.
Cheers.
To the front.
Wait, I want to eat this cheese asparagus. I want to eat the cheese asparagus.
I want to eat it too!
Cheers!
Let's have a toast.
Yes!
Wait a minute.
I'll have a soda.
No way!
The egg is getting dark.
Wait a minute.
Let's do it again.
What are we toasting to today?
To our summer night and exciting winter.
Cheers!
Cheers for the exciting winter! Cheers!
Let's drink!
Cheers!
It looks delicious!
You can eat it.
I'm sorry.
Wait!
So you're going to eat half of it?
There are two of them.
Did you put it sideways? The next day The next day The next day The next day
The next day
The next day The next day Kale! It's good for your body.
Wait a minute! Arin is better!
No, she did it faster.
She's good.
She's a homebody.
Here you go.
She's good.
I'll take your butt off.
No, no.
That's not what I meant.
You're not good at it.
I'm not good at it.
Do you want to take the salad?
No, no.
Take it.
Thank you.
How much is it?
Three.
Yes, this much.
Take the asparagus
And the egg Oh no, can I eat it?
Let's eat
The scallops are good too
But the scallops are not the ones from BBQ
They are really good
They have a very stylish sauce It's not just a We are all summer women.
Yes, we are.
But Kana doesn't go outside at all.
Because her skin is white.
Let's eat.
The asparagus is delicious.
It's delicious.
The ham is delicious.
It's the best.
The ham is delicious. It's the best. The ramen is delicious.
Thank you for your dinner.
It's delicious.
What did you say?
Meat?
I'm eating.
I love ramen.
It's white, but it's okay.
It's white now, but it's okay.
It's so good! Do you like it?
I can eat one.
Rum is good.
It goes well with beer.
You're cutting it.
Is this tomato?
It's good that much. I'm cutting it off. Is this tomato? Is this tomato?
That's how delicious it is.
Eat it. Don't hate it.
Shut up.
It's not like that.
Eat it.
I know that tomatoes are delicious.
I know that and I'm telling you.
It would have been better if you brought a spoon.
Thank you.
I was taken by this side.
Did you say something in the comments? I was waiting. I'm sorry. TikTok? Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
We're ready.
I'll predict.
It's funny, so read it.
It's funny.
Eat tomatoes.
Kale is delicious.
Don't make me talk.
Eat tomatoes.
I'm eating tomatoes.
This is the result of living for 28 years.
The result will change from now on.
Have you been able to eat tomatoes since you were 28 years old?
Yes.
You can eat mushrooms now, right?
Yes. Mushrooms are... You can eat mushrooms now, right? Yes, I can.
Mushrooms are...
What's the difference between mushrooms and tomatoes?
I know, but...
Tomatoes are more essential, right?
Yes, they are.
Tomatoes are a strong enemy.
I agree.
If you don't like them.
The lamb is delicious. The lamb is delicious.
It's soft.
I'm worried about what to do with the lamb.
Is this a comment?
It's a comment.
It says, please change the battery.
It's true. Please change the battery.
The next day The next day
The next day
The next day The next day I'm waiting for everyone to eat. It's delicious. It looks delicious.
It's bigger than that.
It's delicious.
Why?
Why did you stop eating that?
It's delicious.
Everyone is eating that.
Everyone is eating that. Everyone is eating.
Everyone is eating.
Everyone is eating. It's delicious.
What kind of soda do you like?
Shonan Soda.
What about you?
I like Iyoshi Cola.
I used to go to the filming of the movie, World's Mysterious Discovery.
Oh, the one you mentioned?
Yes, the one with the coke.
I made the coke at a cola restaurant in London.
I used to go to Iyoshi Cola.
I heard that the coke has a lot of spices.
What about you, A-chan?
Black beer.
It's like Tokyo white.
It looks delicious.
What about you, Nene-chan?
It's Yonayonabeer.
Let's eat.
The tea is delicious. It's eat. Let's eat. The shiitake mushrooms are delicious.
I know.
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
I'm full.
Can I eat it?
You can eat it today.
I'm full. I have to eat it later.
I'm just eating today. You already ate it. You have to eat more. I'm not sure.
It's super good even if you eat it once in 15 minutes.
I'm sure some people saw it in the middle.
Did you eat the scallops?
It's delicious.
It's so good.
It's the same.
Everyone, I'm going to eat scallops.
It's a waste to eat it.
I'm going to eat the scallops. I'm going to eat the scallops too.
It's good.
Thank you.
The taste doesn't change.
I want to eat it too.
I'm going to eat it in one bite.
In one bite? I'll finish eating and then eat the scallops. In one bite?
It's so good!
It's good to dip the scallops in the sauce.
It's definitely good!
I love happiness.
It's good.
It's good! It's good!
Even if your mouth turns into a scallop, right?
Even if your mouth turns into a scallop.
But it's hard to recover scallop's mouth.
It's hard.
Scallop's mouth.
I've been craving for shiolongbao the other day.
You said that.
I was on the broadcast with Arin,
I thought I had to eat shoronpo today.
I invited my manager to eat shoronpo.
Did you eat it?
I'm satisfied.
I rarely eat shoronpo.
I want to eat it when I'm told to.
I want to eat shoronpo today.
I often eat it. I eat it for about three times a year. I have the image that I often eat shoronbo today. I often eat it.
I often eat it.
I want to eat dumplings.
I bought it at a convenience store.
I want to eat shoronbo.
You sell shoronbo at a convenience store.
It was delicious.
I will eat the salmon.
What are you guys eating?
I wonder what you guys are eating.
What time is it now?
It's past 8 o'clock.
It means that it's past 8.30.
That's right.
I'm getting a lot of comments saying that you're doing your best.
Thank you.
When is it?
September.
I'm doing it on July 8th.
I'm on the show on the 8th.
I see.
Next week.
Next week?
Not at all.
Not today?
Next week.
No.
Next week? September. Next week?
The head of September?
It's different from the head of September.
I don't feel like the date.
Thank you.
It's next week.
Oh, no.
I got a comment.
I don't think I'll practice.
Kanako-chan, you were so pretty in the beauty kit.
Thank you.
You were cute.
Which one do you like?
I like the one from the black dress.
The next day of the black dress?
The next day.
The next day of the black dress.
I forgot. I didn't forget. You didn day... Oh, I forgot.
I didn't forget.
You didn't forget, but you forgot.
Oh, no.
How do you want to be on the show alone?
I want to be a experienced mom.
You should teach your mom to be a mom.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
But what should we do?
I think that's true.
But that's the last week.
I'm nervous.
I'm so nervous.
I was surprised too.
But if we just sing the song of Momoko, you will lose.
That's true.
You will have to balance it.
You will have to make a lot of songs.
It's fun to do the Marlin Blues.
This is the sunflower.
It's still hot in summer.
If you feel like it's still summer, you can do it in the beginning of September.
If it's early September, we can do it. We can do it.
That's true.
We're looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it too.
It's going to be fun.
We're looking forward to our turn.
Shuu-chan took us to Mr. Kowada's school.
Really?
I think he's a good student.
He took us to his school saying,
Thank you for your time.
I think we can meet again.
That's right.
It's amazing. That's amazing.
I'm happy to be able to see your live.
It's been a while since we met.
That's right.
Last time, we had a break.
It was in North Korea. It was in North Kyushu.
That's right.
We had a break.
Yabati is there too.
That's right.
It's the best.
I went to Rocky this year.
You went to Rocky?
Yes. It's the best.
Yes, because it's the best.
It's perfect.
On the last day of Rocky, 100,000 people fell.
What?
It's a lot of people.
Really?
But that's right.
Because Sadan said he wanted to see it.
Because Sadan said he wanted to see it. Everyone wants to see it. I want to see it. It's amazing. 100,000 people fell. I heard that Satane Satabe is graduating soon.
I want to see everyone.
That's amazing.
100,000 people are coming to the school.
What?
That's amazing.
I'm nervous.
I'm expecting everyone to come.
Some people are saying, I got it.
Salmon, salmon.
Take the salmon.
It's okay.
Wait, wait.
The meat is coming.
100,000 people are coming.
That's amazing.
I really want everyone would come.
Do you want to do this?
I'm surprised that the person who got it was really surprised.
The meat is coming.
Meat!
I did it!
I'm so happy to see you.
Thank you!
Salmon is delicious!
Salmon sauce is really delicious.
I've never eaten it before. It's so good. The sauce is so good. I've never tried it before.
It's so good.
It's so sweet and nice.
It's sweet but garlicy.
It's good.
I'm going to eat something.
What?
Excuse me. What do you want? What is it? It's that one, right? Oh, sorry, what is it?
What color?
I think it's salmon.
But I know the answer to all four.
Really?
It's for you, Kana.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Naori, what did you say? Excuse me. How many days have you been there?
I went to the day of AIMYON.
I went with Pornograffty.
I went with 10.
10?
I always check.
Thank you.
Onions.
It's a! It's onion!
It's onion!
I'm happy.
The eggplant is also here.
The vegetables are delicious.
Thank you!
It's huge! It's huge!
It's huge!
Itadakimasu!
I'll show you.
Ta-da!
It's amazing!
Let's eat paprika.
It looks delicious.
Itadakimasu! The meat is amazing. Let's eat paprika! It looks delicious! Let's eat!
The meat is amazing!
It looks delicious!
I'm busy!
I'm full!
I know!
I know that!
Oh my god!
Is this zucchini?
Which one?
This one.
I love zucchini!
What do you mean?
It's in the back.
It's under here.
It's like a small chicken dish.
Kanta is already full.
Kotori-chan.
Oh! The demon is here! Can I have some? I'm not hungry yet. You're already full. Oh, I dropped it.
I'm laughing.
Are you full?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
It's not heavy.
Is it heavy?
It's okay.
Let's eat this.
I don't need it.
Thank you. Itadakimasu. Let's try this one. No, I don't want it. No, I don't want it.
Thank you.
Itadakimasu.
I'll squeeze the mayonnaise.
Wait, the meat is delicious.
Not this one?
It's just seasoned.
Oh, it ate meat.
This is the best.
This is a very good taste.
Can you see this?
This is medium rare.
I eat zucchini.
I eat this.
I eat this. I'm going to eat. I'm going to eat.
I'm going to eat.
The meat is really good.
I want to show it to the viewers.
It's soft.
It's good.
It's summer.
I'm happy.
The outside wind is coming in.
I feel summer.
It's so good.
I'm wandering in if I can sing it. I'm not sure if I can sing it. I'm not sure if I can sing it.
I'm not sure if I can sing it.
I'm not sure if I can sing it. I I don't think I should use it. If you use it, you're out.
I think I can't.
I don't think I can sing.
I think I can sing.
It's delicious. I'm happy.
The harmony is coming.
Is it?
Yes, the harmony of the end of summer.
It's coming.
I'm sweating again.
I know. It's hot. It's hot. It's coming. I'm sweating again. I know! It's hot!
It's hot.
The zucchini is so good.
I want to eat zucchini.
It's a perfect way to eat.
Right?
Everyone wants to eat meat.
I want to eat it.
Isn't zucchini water?
Yes, it is.
Water is better than cucumber.
Cucumber is also good.
But it's like...
It's like...
It's good.
Why?
I'm sorry. You're going to get so absorbed in it.
Yeah.
It's that good.
Drink it.
Can I drink more?
Yeah.
Drink it.
We were talking about something else on the radio the other day.
What was it?
We were talking about how you were so sluggish.
You're the most affected by the I was scared. I couldn't breathe. I was dying.
When I get drunk, I feel everything in my eyes as if they are my love.
I was like, so cute.
I couldn't stop thinking about my baby.
It was so hard.
That photo is still there.
And it was at the festival?
Yes, at the festival.
And there was an artist I really wanted to see, but she was taken away.
She was taken away? That's crazy.
She was taken away saying, I'm going home.
I noticed.
And she stayed until the end.
She was playing at night.
Yes, she was playing at night.
I didn't want to notice.
Was she here?
Yes, she was. That's good. I don't like it because I'm tired. Which one did you like? I liked the one in the middle.
I see.
I don't like it because I'm tired.
It's not that bad if you're with your friends.
I was really drunk at that time.
I was relieved.
Why were you relieved at the party?
I heard that if Shiori was next to you, you would get drunk at a high rate. If Shi is next to me, I think she'll get drunk.
If Shinta is next to me, I think she'll get drunk.
I have that image.
I've been to a bar several times.
Poor girl.
I don't drink that much.
I feel calm.
It's fun.
It's fun. It's fun.
Music and alcohol are a perfect match.
It's a luxury.
I think it's fun for people who can drink alcohol.
I feel like I'm sweating.
But I can't drink water.
That's why I'm drinking. But you don't get a water supply. I'm drinking tea, but I feel like I'm drinking it separately.
But I think it looks good.
Let's enjoy it moderately.
Who's talking?
No doubt.
It's delicious. It's delicious.
It's delicious.
I'll do it a little more.
I'm asking you.
I'm asking you to do it.
I'll eat it.
I wonder if I can eat it. I wonder if I can eat it. What about you, Ani? I wonder if I'll eat it.
What did you say?
I already ordered two cups.
Oh, really?
It's hot, so I'll drink it while I'm drinking.
You can drink it while you're drinking.
But I don't drink it while I'm drinking.
That's right. I'm not a pink person.
I can tell you this.
I don't want to be drunk again.
I'm a drunk person.
You can control yourself.
I'll do my best.
Let's go home together.
Let's go home together. Let's go home together.
I'm done drinking.
It's so fun.
I'm having fun.
I want to do it again.
If you notice, say no.
I hate it.
It's too hard.
It's too much. It's too much. It's like a speech.
What happens if Erlin is drunk?
I've seen Erlin.
I've seen him.
Erlin is a f***ing f***er.
But he's a drunk girl. I don't get so upset.
Stop it, Reni-chan. Don't compare me.
I know you're going to be a good girl from now on.
But I was drunk.
But I remember him.
Yeah, but you don't remember most of the time.
You don't remember most of the time.
But even if I don't remember, I always tell my friends around me,
Are you okay?
I'm often told that I'm okay.
So the camera camera is on.
But Ari was a little more interesting.
It was more messy than usual.
It's not good.
But that's when you get stronger.
It's always more messy.
It's hard. I'm always the one who gets the most angry. I'm always the one who gets the most angry. You're always the one who gets the most angry.
You're always the one who gets the most angry.
What happens when Hana-chan gets drunk?
I get sleepy.
You get cute.
You get cute. You get cute. I feel like a baby when I'm drunk. Really? I feel sleepy.
You're sleepy.
I close my eyes quietly.
I think she's sleepy.
Yeah.
I feel sleepy.
I don't have a pattern to be sleepy.
What?
I wonder.
I get really sleepy sometimes.
Do you? I wonder. I get sleepy a lot depending on the day. Do you?
I do.
But Aori is getting stronger because she's drinking.
Yes.
I felt like I was getting sleepy faster.
I feel sleepy more and more.
Shi-chan is surprisingly strong.
She's not strong.
She's not very strong, but I'm stronger than I thought.
I don't like alcohol, so I don't drink.
I think people who don't drink at all.
I don't drink at all, but I get sleepy in the end.
My face turns red.
My face turns red in the middle of the first drink.
I don't want to drink at a place where I don't want to drink.
Totoro, I don't want to drink.
What?
I really want to see Totoro today.
It starts in 6 minutes. I really want to see Totoro in the New Year's Eve. It starts in 6 minutes.
That's right. I really want to see Totoro.
Totoro is...
No, it's okay. I recorded it.
I want to see Totoro.
Totoro is...
Isn't it summer?
I see Totoro at this time of year.
I want to see it regularly.
Then...
It's time to go.
It's too late.
Let's announce it around here. It's time to go. It's so cute.
Let's announce it around here.
It's about time.
Yes.
Is it over?
You haven't said anything.
December 21st, 2020
Saturday
Sunday
I will hold the Momoiro Christmas 2024.
The venue is Saitama Super Arena.
Please.
Please. And The venue is Saitama Super Arena. Please come.
The 22nd CD single, RENASALE SERENA DAY will be released on August 28 next week.
Please look at the real one.
This is the actual CD.
The illustration is very cute.
The black and white version is the opposite.
This one?
The wooden one.
The case version is our color.
There are two colors.
Please check it out.
I'm a little bit of a spoiler.
I haven't seen Rimuru become a ninja yet.
I'm a ninja too.
I haven't seen it yet.
It's a spoiler in the opening.
I thought so.
What is this? What is this person like the a spoiler. I thought so too. I was like, what is this?
What is this person?
Ai-ni, today?
Yes.
From 23 o'clock today, we will broadcast a special anime.
I have to watch it.
I'm really chasing after it.
Can't you watch it yet?
I have to watch it.
And, I'm happy thatisode anime tie-up!
Thank you!
The anime is the opening theme song of the anime,
and we will sing the song,
We will sing the song,
The song is written by Kenji Otsuki,
and we are the producers.
We will play some parts in the music video,
so please listen to it. Please listen to it.
Thank you.
This anime will be broadcasted from October.
There are many in the fall.
I'm happy.
And I. And then, I will be on the live broadcast of the official idol channel NICO DOL run by NICO NICO on August 31, 19.
I will do it.
The title is a live broadcast that does not give up on summer.
I haven't given up on it yet. We haven't given up on it yet.
But, including today, I haven't done it yet.
I wonder what it is.
I want to do it.
Please watch it.
Please check the website for details.
Please.
Is that all?
That's all.
So, we'll start the Totoro show in two minutes.
Match the Totoro.
It's an important memory. How many times have you shown us?
It doesn't matter how many times I see you.
I want to see you many times.
It's really a no-cut version.
But it's the second time.
It's the second time-cut version. But the second one is here. The second one is here.
Let's drink.
The second one.
I'm going to put it in.
Oh, that's right.
I did it.
Oh, I did it.
I put too much in.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Thank you.
Cheers. Cheers!
Cheers!
What is that?
This is China Blue.
China Blue.
What is that? Is it a cocktail? This is China Blue.
Cocktail? Cocktail.
What about you?
Samburia.
It's something sangria.
It's only one minute before the end of the show.
One minute before the end of the show?
I'm so happy to see you in the bath.
I haven't seen you in years. I'm so happy to see her in the bath. What is it?
I haven't seen her for years.
I want to see her.
You are Totoro.
I wanted to hear that.
I'm not good at it.
It's Mei.
I wanted to hear that.
That line is impressive.
I like the line,
I'm the main idiot. I like the main part more.
The main part is Satsuki.
I got it.
Good.
It's 21 o'clock.
Goodbye everyone.
We didn't talk about anything.
Too fast!
It was a live stream with no content.
Let's do a second time while watching Totoro.
We're going home.
Why are you going home?
We'll see you at the TenSura after this.
Yes, we'll be at TenSura.
The opening will be aired, so please watch it with us.
And please check the schedule of Momocuri.
The ticket sales will start from 9.11.
Oh, it's already started!
Oh, it's already started?
It's already started.
Oh, no!
There's an important announcement from Totoro. Why! Why is it TOTORO's announcement?
Hurry up!
The ticket sales, the ticket sales for Momocuri have started.
Yes.
Yes, we'll do our best to make a live performance.
We'll do our best.
Please check out the schedule.
Please come and play.
Well then, everyone, let's meet again.
Bye bye! Bye bye!
Thank you for all the people who helped us!
Thank you!
Bye bye! Thank you.
Thank you.